[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "Why have you decided to face the music?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "have", "you", "decided", "to", "face", "the", "music", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "Well, coming from you, Piers, that means a great deal to me, and I thank you for being so gracious.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "coming", "from", "you", ",", "Piers", ",", "that", "means", "a", "great", "deal", "to", "me", ",", "and", "I", "thank", "you", "for", "being", "so", "gracious", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "EX", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "And I think a lot of people feel, wow, how could this have happened to them?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "think", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "feel", ",", "wow", ",", "how", "could", "this", "have", "happened", "to", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Well, I think -- I think you've hit the nail on the head right near there, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "you", "'ve", "hit", "the", "nail", "on", "the", "head", "right", "near", "there", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "And what -- I suppose what I'm getting at, does it really make sense to you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "--", "I", "suppose", "what", "I", "'m", "getting", "at", ",", "does", "it", "really", "make", "sense", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "I don't know if any of it makes sense, to be quite honest, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "any", "of", "it", "makes", "sense", ",", "to", "be", "quite", "honest", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "How can you not love somebody?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "you", "not", "love", "somebody", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "This is making me even sadder.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "making", "me", "even", "sadder", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "CC", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "TO", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "And but I was never made to feel so because they had four kids of their own, and those were the most important years of my childhood, because they -- it was that harmony that I would constantly refer back to, because my life after that, my mother -- my biological mother came to take me when I was four years old, and it was this strange woman who I'd never seen before.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "but", "I", "was", "never", "made", "to", "feel", "so", "because", "they", "had", "four", "kids", "of", "their", "own", ",", "and", "those", "were", "the", "most", "important", "years", "of", "my", "childhood", ",", "because", "they", "--", "it", "was", "that", "harmony", "that", "I", "would", "constantly", "refer", "back", "to", ",", "because", "my", "life", "after", "that", ",", "my", "mother", "--", "my", "biological", "mother", "came", "to", "take", "me", "when", "I", "was", "four", "years", "old", ",", "and", "it", "was", "this", "strange", "woman", "who", "I", "'d", "never", "seen", "before", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Brixton"]}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "Do you remember that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Yes, I remember that moment very, very well, because I remember she -- I remember -- I remember screaming all the way home on the bus to Brixton, which is where she was living with her new boyfriend.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "remember", "that", "moment", "very", ",", "very", "well", ",", "because", "I", "remember", "she", "--", "I", "remember", "--", "I", "remember", "screaming", "all", "the", "way", "home", "on", "the", "bus", "to", "Brixton", ",", "which", "is", "where", "she", "was", "living", "with", "her", "new", "boyfriend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "Biological father?", "question_tokens": ["Biological", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "Yes, my biological father, he came to take me and I live with him and his new wife, my stepmother, who I love dearly, and that was pretty much when the hell started.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "my", "biological", "father", ",", "he", "came", "to", "take", "me", "and", "I", "live", "with", "him", "and", "his", "new", "wife", ",", "my", "stepmother", ",", "who", "I", "love", "dearly", ",", "and", "that", "was", "pretty", "much", "when", "the", "hell", "started", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "By your father?", "question_tokens": ["By", "your", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "TO", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", ":", "EX", "VBD", "CD", "NN", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "CD", "WP", "MD", "VB", ":", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RP", "IN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "When you say thrashed, how?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "say", "thrashed", ",", "how", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "Well, my father used to -- my father used to -- he used to -- there was one point where my father cut up six what must be -- must have been meter-length pieces of twine, something that you hang the curtain up with, and because I'd been suspended from school.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "father", "used", "to", "--", "my", "father", "used", "to", "--", "he", "used", "to", "--", "there", "was", "one", "point", "where", "my", "father", "cut", "up", "six", "what", "must", "be", "--", "must", "have", "been", "meter-length", "pieces", "of", "twine", ",", "something", "that", "you", "hang", "the", "curtain", "up", "with", ",", "and", "because", "I", "'d", "been", "suspended", "from", "school", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PDT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Why should you be, after all this?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "should", "you", "be", ",", "after", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Well, when you have kids, you realize that it's not the easiest gig in the world, but, yes, you're absolutely right, for all intents and purposes, I was a child.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "when", "you", "have", "kids", ",", "you", "realize", "that", "it", "'s", "not", "the", "easiest", "gig", "in", "the", "world", ",", "but", ",", "yes", ",", "you", "'re", "absolutely", "right", ",", "for", "all", "intents", "and", "purposes", ",", "I", "was", "a", "child", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Is that one of the reasons why when you get smeared with this volcanic temper thing, it really annoys you, because actually the last thing you would be is like that, because of the way you were brought up?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "one", "of", "the", "reasons", "why", "when", "you", "get", "smeared", "with", "this", "volcanic", "temper", "thing", ",", "it", "really", "annoys", "you", ",", "because", "actually", "the", "last", "thing", "you", "would", "be", "is", "like", "that", ",", "because", "of", "the", "way", "you", "were", "brought", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "No, the reason is, is that I don't want my kids to ever see that.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "the", "reason", "is", ",", "is", "that", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "my", "kids", "to", "ever", "see", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "Are they aware of what's happening?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "aware", "of", "what", "'s", "happening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "You've told them?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "told", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "Of course we have.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "we", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "How good was he?", "question_tokens": ["How", "good", "was", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Well, exactly, that's what I had to say.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "exactly", ",", "that", "'s", "what", "I", "had", "to", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "What is the reality check about Barack Obama?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "reality", "check", "about", "Barack", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "Well, you mentioned black president.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "mentioned", "black", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "As you were preparing this album, did you have any concept that that was how this was all going to play out?", "question_tokens": ["As", "you", "were", "preparing", "this", "album", ",", "did", "you", "have", "any", "concept", "that", "that", "was", "how", "this", "was", "all", "going", "to", "play", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "WRB", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "You get the irony of this?", "question_tokens": ["You", "get", "the", "irony", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "That, in of itself, probably gives you some insight into who I am as a person.", "answer_tokens": ["That", ",", "in", "of", "itself", ",", "probably", "gives", "you", "some", "insight", "into", "who", "I", "am", "as", "a", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Were you aware when you -- as I say, when you put this together, was it anything to do with what was happening with your life at that moment?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "aware", "when", "you", "--", "as", "I", "say", ",", "when", "you", "put", "this", "together", ",", "was", "it", "anything", "to", "do", "with", "what", "was", "happening", "with", "your", "life", "at", "that", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Total coincidence?", "question_tokens": ["Total", "coincidence", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "No, because we -- we -- I wasn't the only person who picked those songs.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "because", "we", "--", "we", "--", "I", "was", "n't", "the", "only", "person", "who", "picked", "those", "songs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2009"], "PERSON": ["John"]}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Tell me why you decided, after all this time, to write it?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "why", "you", "decided", ",", "after", "all", "this", "time", ",", "to", "write", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "Well, I had done an interview -- a TV interview in 2009 about John's charity Reaching Up.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "had", "done", "an", "interview", "--", "a", "TV", "interview", "in", "2009", "about", "John", "'s", "charity", "Reaching", "Up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "RP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "How would you describe the relationship, as you saw it develop?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "describe", "the", "relationship", ",", "as", "you", "saw", "it", "develop", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "You know, as I saw it develop, they sort of started out -- they had this little camaraderie.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "as", "I", "saw", "it", "develop", ",", "they", "sort", "of", "started", "out", "--", "they", "had", "this", "little", "camaraderie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "But did she find it tough, do you think, being in the public gaze?", "question_tokens": ["But", "did", "she", "find", "it", "tough", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "being", "in", "the", "public", "gaze", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Initially, I think it was very difficult because it was -- once they got married, it somehow amped up.", "answer_tokens": ["Initially", ",", "I", "think", "it", "was", "very", "difficult", "because", "it", "was", "--", "once", "they", "got", "married", ",", "it", "somehow", "amped", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Caroline"]}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "Have you stayed in touch with the family at all?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "stayed", "in", "touch", "with", "the", "family", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "I mean, I see Caroline from time to time at events or restaurants or -- it's always really nice to see her.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "see", "Caroline", "from", "time", "to", "time", "at", "events", "or", "restaurants", "or", "--", "it", "'s", "always", "really", "nice", "to", "see", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Do you know how they reacted to the book, the family?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "how", "they", "reacted", "to", "the", "book", ",", "the", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "No, I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "What do you think he would have been doing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "he", "would", "have", "been", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "He certainly talked about running for office at some point.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "certainly", "talked", "about", "running", "for", "office", "at", "some", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBD", "RB", ",", "``", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 489, "question": "And what will your lasting memory be of him?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "will", "your", "lasting", "memory", "be", "of", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "NN", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "Well, I think, you know, the legacy he left that was unfortunately, \"George.\"", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "legacy", "he", "left", "that", "was", "unfortunately", ",", "``", "George", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]